sitevacuum.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy - SiteVacuum.com

###  SiteVacuum Principles

We built SiteVacuum to make it easy for you to use. We also understand your information and privacy is important and sensitive and that why we made sure that: 

**1\. You Own your Information**

You own your information, and we own what you decide to share with us. If you'd like us to destroy this information, we will remove your user profile at any time if you request it by e-mailing us [support@SiteVacuum.com](mailto:support@SiteVacuum.com). We'll do our best to remove any information that is personally attributable to you within 10 days. 

**2\. We ask for information from you, only when we must and in order to provide you quality service**

Types of information you may wish to provide us in order to get the best services possible: 

     **Registration Information** – When you sign up for a SiteVacuum account, we ask you for personal information, including your name, e-mail address and an account password. You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case SiteVacuum may not be able to provide those services to you. 
     **Information for fulfilling your requests** \- Certain functions are impossible to fulfill without getting some information from you. We ask for information only so we can fulfill your request and to provide you quality service, for example registration. 
     **SiteVacuum cookies** – When you visit the SiteVacuum website & services, we send a small file to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. This file is called a cookie. We use cookies to improve the quality of our Service by storing your preferences. Your browser is probably set up by default to accept cookies, including SiteVacuum cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you when a cookie is being sent to your computer. You should be aware, however, that some of SiteVacuum 's features may not function properly if you disable cookies on your computer. 
     **Standard browser information** – When you visit the SiteVacuum website and use our features and Services, your browser sends information normally just like it does whenever you visit any website. Our servers may record this information that as your computer's browser (not our plug-in) sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your computer's browser. 

**3\. Information Discloser & Usage**

SiteVacuum may use your personal information without your prior consent when we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of SiteVacuum, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. From time to time, we may supplement Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Website with information collected by third parties. 

We will not collect or use personal information for purposes other than those described in this Policy unless we have obtained your prior consent. 

**California has passed legislation requiring certain specific disclosures be made available to California residents who use the Internet and provide information that may be used for marketing purposes. That legislation requires any business that discloses a customer's personal information to any third party for direct marketing purposes to provide the customer a method for obtaining the names, addresses and certain other specified details of anyone who might have received that personal information. If you are a California resident you may request this information from SiteVacuum by writing to SiteVacuum, 1738 Pearl Street, Suite 202, Boulder, CO 80302 Attn: California Privacy Rights or by sending an e-mail to** [ support@SiteVacuum.com](mailto:support@SiteVacuum.com). **SiteVacuum is not obligated to respond to more than one such request from you per calendar year.**

If you are visiting SiteVacuum from outside of the United States, please be advised that your information will be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States, may might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our Services, you consent to the transfer of your information to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Policy. 

**4\. Information Security**

SiteVacuum takes appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data that you share and that we collect we store. These security measures include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store your personal data. 

Furthermore, we restrict access to personal information only to SiteVacuum employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. Unfortunately, no security system can be 100% secured; accordingly, SiteVacuum cannot guarantee the security of any information provided to us in connection with the information that we collect through our website. 

**Still Have Questions?**   
If you have additional questions about this policy or your privacy or  
feel free to contact us at [support@SiteVacuum.com](mailto:support@SiteVacuum.com).
